<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workflows on gg</title>
    <link>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workflows on gg</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 08:48:58 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Locally</title>
      <link>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/local/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 13:49:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/local/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whether you are working by yourself or with others, the workflow for making
changes on your local machine stays the same. This guide is primarily aimed at
those who are new to version control, but is also useful for seasoned version
control users trying to see how gg stacks up to their current tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fork and Pull</title>
      <link>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/fork/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 13:29:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/fork/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The fork and pull model &lt;a href=&#34;https://guides.github.com/introduction/flow/&#34;&gt;popularized by GitHub&lt;/a&gt; is the most common way
to use gg. When using this model, the project has a primary repository that
only the maintainers of the project have write access to.  Contributors make
changes by sharing a cloned repository (called the fork) with new branches.
Contributors send pull requests to maintainers, who then review the code and
merge in the changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shared Repository</title>
      <link>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/shared/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 08:21:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/shared/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.github.com/articles/about-collaborative-development-models/&#34;&gt;shared repository model&lt;/a&gt;, the source of truth is a single
shared repository. This pattern is popular with individuals and smaller teams.
Each developer clones to a repository on their own machine and makes their
changes. When they are ready to share, they push to a branch on the single
shared repository. If they are using pull requests, each change goes onto a
distinct &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.github.com/articles/about-branches/&#34;&gt;branch&lt;/a&gt; for review. Otherwise, usually commits go directly to the
default branch (usually &lt;code&gt;master&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gerrit</title>
      <link>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/gerrit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 08:48:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zombiezen.github.io/gg/workflow/gerrit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some popular open source projects use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gerritcodereview.com/&#34;&gt;Gerrit&lt;/a&gt;, a code review tool, to
manage code contributions. Examples include &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://source.android.com/&#34;&gt;Android&lt;/a&gt;, and
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chromium.org/&#34;&gt;Chromium&lt;/a&gt;. Gerrit has a somewhat unique model for receiving changes that
involves amending commits and pushing to specially formatted ref names.
Developers using Gerrit usually build shortcuts on top of Git to manage this
complexity, but gg has built-in support for Gerrit. gg makes working with
Gerrit as easy as other Git workflows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>